goeshow.com 2019-04-06

# eShow: Event Management Solutions

Your data privacy and security are important to us. So we will continue to update our privacy policy to make it even more transparent and give you more clarity and control over how we process and use personal data when delivering our world-class products and services.

## GDPR

**Compliance with Data Protection Principles**

**Accountability and Consent**

Netronix Corporation, DBA eShow will provide data collectors/clients with reasonable mechanisms/tools for GDPR compliance.

For personal information, Netronix Corporation, DBA eShow will offer data collectors/clients and their users the opportunity to choose (opt-in) whether their personal information is (a) to be disclosed to a non-agent third party, or (b) to be used for a purpose other than the purpose for which it was originally collected or subsequently authorized by the individual.

For sensitive personal information, Netronix Corporation, DBA eShow will give data collectors/clients and their users the opportunity to affirmatively and explicitly (opt-in) consent to the disclosure of the information to a non- agent third party or the use of the information for a purpose other than the purpose for which it was originally collected or subsequently authorized by the individual.

## PRIVACY SHIELD OVERVIEW

The EU-U.S. and Swiss-U.S. Privacy Shield Frameworks were designed by the U.S. Department of Commerce, and the European Commission and Swiss Administration, respectively, to provide companies on both sides of the Atlantic with a mechanism to comply with data protection requirements when transferring personal data from the European Union and Switzerland to the United States in support of transatlantic commerce. On July 12, 2016, the European Commission deemed the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework adequate to enable data transfers under EU law (see the adequacy determination). <http://europa.eu/rapid/press-release_IP-16-2461_en.htm>

On January 12, 2017, the Swiss Government announced the approval of the Swiss-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework as a valid legal mechanism to comply with Swiss requirements when transferring personal data from Switzerland to the United States. See the statements from the Swiss Federal Council <https://www.admin.ch/gov/en/start/documentation/media-releases.msg-id-65210.html>

and Swiss Federal Data Protection and Information Commissioner <https://www.edoeb.admin.ch/datenschutz/00626/00753/01405/01406/index.html?lang=en>

Netronix Corporation, DBA eShow complies with the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework and the Swiss-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information from European Union member countries and Switzerland. Netronix Corporation, DBA eShow has certified that it adheres to the Privacy Shield Framework Principles of notice, choice, onward transfer, security, data integrity, access, and enforcement. To learn more about the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield and Swiss-U.S. Privacy Shield programs, please visit: <https://www.privacyshield.gov/welcome> and to view Netronix Corporation, DBA eShow's Privacy Shield certification, please visit [https://www.privacyshield.gov/participant](https://www.privacyshield.gov/participant?id=a2zt00000008PhYAAU&status=Active).

## Independent Recourse Mechanism for Privacy Shield Complaints

**Dispute Resolution**

Within the scope of this privacy notice, if a privacy complaint or dispute cannot be resolved through Netronix Corporation, DBA eShow's internal processes, Netronix Corporation, DBA eShow has agreed to participate in the [VeraSafe Privacy Shield Dispute Resolution Procedure](https://www.verasafe.com/privacy-services/dispute-resolution/privacy-shield-dispute-procedure/). Subject to the terms of the VeraSafe Privacy Shield Dispute Resolution Procedure, VeraSafe will provide appropriate recourse free of charge to you. To file a complaint with VeraSafe under the Privacy Shield Dispute Resolution Procedure, please submit the required information to VeraSafe here: <https://www.verasafe.com/privacy-services/dispute-resolution/submit-dispute/>

Netronix Corporation, DBA eShow is also subject to the investigatory and enforcement powers of the Federal Trade Commission with respect to the Framework. In addition, under certain conditions, more fully described on the Privacy Shield website at <https://www.privacyshield.gov/article?id=How-to-Submit-a-Complaint>, EU data subjects may invoke binding arbitration for non-monetary issues when other dispute resolution procedures have been exhausted.

In compliance with the Privacy Shield Principles, Netronix Corporation, DBA eShow commits to resolve complaints about our collection or use of your personal information. EU individuals with inquiries or complaints regarding our Privacy Shield policy should first contact the corporate office.

In cases of onward transfer to third parties of data of EU or Swiss individuals, received pursuant to the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield and Swiss-U.S. Privacy Shield, Netronix Corporation, DBA eShow is potentially liable.

By email to:  

Netronix Corporation, DBA eShow  
Attn: Privacy Policy Officer  
5 Executive Court, Suite 2  
South Barrington, IL 60010

## PRIVACY SHIELD POLICY FOR CONSUMER DATA

Netronix Corporation, DBA eShow is committed to upholding the highest ethical standards in its business practices and strives to collect, use and disclose personal information in a manner consistent with the laws of the countries in which it does business. The new EU-U.S. Privacy Shield and the Swiss-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework sets forth the privacy principles that Netronix Corporation, DBA eShow follows with respect to personal consumer information transferred from the European Economic Area (EEA) (which includes the twenty-eight member states of the European Union (EU) plus Iceland, Liechtenstein and Norway) and from Switzerland to the United States.

## SCOPE

This EU-U.S. Privacy Shield Policy (the "Policy") applies to all personal information received from consumers by Netronix Corporation, DBA eShow in the United States from the European Economic Area and from Switzerland, in any format including electronic, paper or verbal.

## BUSINESS USE

We use your Personal Information primarily to facilitate our ongoing and proposed business dealings with you (“Business Use”). This includes to: (1) process business transactions with us that you initiate; (2) establish and maintain customer accounts so that we may provide products or services of ours requested by you or your company; (3) register you as a user of these products or services so that you may access them through our Sites or otherwise; (4) communicate with you about updates, maintenance, outages or other technical matters concerning these products or services; (5) provide you with training regarding usage of these products or services; (6) notify you about changes to any of the policies and procedures for use of these products or services; (7) verify the accuracy of account and technical contact information we have on file for you and your company in relation to these products or services; and (8) respond to questions or inquiries that you or your company may have about our products or services. We also may use your Personal Information as required for us to comply with laws and regulations relating to the products or services that we provide in any of the jurisdictions in which we operate, including the United States, and we may use Usage Information internally within Netronix Corporation, DBA eShow to help us improve our products or services, or to develop new products or services.

## DEFINITIONS

For purposes of this Policy, the following definitions shall apply:

"Netronix Corporation, DBA eShow" means Netronix Corporation, DBA eShow, its successors, subsidiaries, divisions and groups in the United States.

"Agent" means any third party that collects or uses personal information under the instructions of, and solely for, Netronix Corporation, DBA eShow or to which Netronix Corporation, DBA eShow discloses personal information for use on Netronix Corporation, DBA eShow's behalf. Such as: (1) hosting our Sites; (2) designing and/or operating certain features available through our Sites; (3) sending emails and other communications relating to our products or services; (4) fulfilling and processing orders for our products or services; (5) assisting with promotions and conferences relating to our products or services, or those of our business partners; (6) providing analytic services, such as in relation to the tracking of usage of our Sites; or (7) performing other administrative services for us. We may provide these Data Processors with access to your Personal Information in order for them to complete a requested transaction or otherwise perform services for us or for you on our behalf. Prior to allowing our Agents to access your Personal Information, we will enter into a data protection agreement or addendum (“DPA”) with them to ensure that they handle and process the information in accordance with this Privacy Policy and applicable law as instructed by Netronix Corporation, DBA eShow.

“Personal Information” means any information relating to an identified individual, or to an individual who can be identified, directly or indirectly, by reference to an identification number or to one or more factors specific to his or her physical, physiological, mental, economic, cultural or social identity. Personal Information does not include information that is anonymized. Personal Information does not include corporate information that relates to an organization but not to an individual, such as a corporate name, corporate address or general corporate phone number.

"Sensitive personal information" means personal information that reveals race, ethnic origin, political opinions, religious or philosophical beliefs, or trade union membership, or that concerns health or sex life. In addition, Netronix Corporation, DBA eShow will treat as sensitive personal information any information received from a third party where that third party treats and identifies the information as sensitive.

“Website Usage Information” In addition to Personal Information that you choose to submit to us, whenever you visit or interact with our Sites, we may collect or store information about your interaction with our Sites (“Usage Information”). This Usage Information may include:

  * your IP address or any other unique identifier assigned to the device that you use to access our Sites;
  * the functionality and characteristics of your device, including type of browser, operating system and hardware, mobile network information and in some cases location information;
  * the URL that referred you to our Sites, if any;
  * your activities on our Sites, such as which web pages you visit, what terms you searched within our Sites and which links within our Sites that you click on; and
  * the time of day that you visited our Sites and how long your visit lasted.

Usage Information is typically anonymous information. However, if it is combined with your Personal Information in a manner that reasonably allows it to be associated with your identity, or is otherwise considered Personal Information under applicable law, it will be treated as Personal Information under this Privacy Policy

"Cookies" are small pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computer's hard drive. Netronix Corporation, DBA eShow uses Cookies to provide useful features to our customers. Netronix Corporation, DBA eShow Cookies do not contain any personally identifying information. Your web browser may or may not be set to notify you when you are about to accept a Cookie. If you refuse to accept a Cookie while on Netronix Corporation, DBA eShow websites, you may not be able to access portions of the site.

"Information We Receive From Third Parties". We may receive Personal Information about you from third parties who recommend or suggest that we contact you for business purposes. This includes basic contact information about you, such as your name, company name, title, address, phone number, fax number and email address. It may also include information on the products or services you have shown interest in or may be interested in purchasing from us, as well as information on other companies or individuals with whom you do business. We may also obtain Personal Information about you from third parties in connection with business transactions you initiate with us, such as through credit verification or other processes related to the transaction.

"Links to Other Websites and Applications". The Sites may contain various links to, as well as plug-ins or widgets from, social media and other third-party websites or applications, which may provide additional information, goods, services and/or promotions. These third-party websites or applications are owned and operated independently of Netronix Corporation, DBA eShow, and may have their own separate privacy and data collection practices. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of any third party. Therefore, you should review their privacy policies and practices prior to interacting with their websites or applications, using any of their tools, or sharing any of your Personal Information with them.

"Business Transfers". Netronix Corporation, DBA eShow or any part of its business, including our Sites, may be sold at some point in the future. Should this occur, your Personal Information may be transferred to a subsequent owner, co-owner or operator of the business unit or Site. We also may disclose and transfer your Personal Information in connection with a corporate merger, consolidation, restructuring, the sale of stock or assets, or other corporate change, including, without limitation, during the course of any due diligence process. In all such cases, this Privacy Policy will continue to govern the use and disclosure of such information. "Children" The Sites are intended for business use, and we do not knowingly collect any Personal Information from children younger than the age of thirteen (13), or from children, who do not have the necessary ability to foresee the consequence of their data being processed, as required by applicable law.

## PRIVACY PRINCIPLES

The privacy principles in this Policy are based on the EU-U.S. and Swiss-U.S. Privacy Shield Frameworks.

**NOTICE:** Where Netronix Corporation, DBA eShow collects personal information directly from individuals in the EEA, it will inform them about the purposes for which it collects and uses personal information about them and the choices and means, if any, Netronix Corporation, DBA eShow offers individuals for limiting the use and disclosure of their personal information. Notice will be provided in clear and conspicuous language when individuals are first asked to provide personal information to Netronix Corporation, DBA eShow, or as soon as practicable thereafter, and in any event before Netronix Corporation, DBA eShow uses or discloses the information for a purpose other than that for which it was originally collected or discloses information to a non-agent third party.

Where Netronix Corporation, DBA eShow receives personal information from its subsidiaries, affiliates or other entities in the EEA, it will use and disclose such information in accordance with the notices provided by such entities and the choices made by the individuals to whom such personal information relates.

**CHOICE:** For personal information, Netronix Corporation, DBA eShow will offer individuals the opportunity to choose (opt-in) whether their personal information is (a) to be disclosed to a non-agent third party, or (b) to be used for a purpose other than the purpose for which it was originally collected or subsequently authorized by the individual.

For sensitive personal information, Netronix Corporation, DBA eShow will give individuals the opportunity to affirmatively and explicitly (opt-in) consent to the disclosure of the information to a non- agent third party or the use of the information for a purpose other than the purpose for which it was originally collected or subsequently authorized by the individual.

Netronix Corporation, DBA eShow will provide individuals with reasonable mechanisms to exercise their choices.

**DATA INTEGRITY:** Netronix Corporation, DBA eShow will use personal information only in ways that are compatible with the purposes for which it was collected or subsequently authorized by the individual. Netronix Corporation, DBA eShow will take reasonable steps to ensure that personal information is relevant to its intended use, accurate, complete, and current. We will only collect and store personal information that is relevant to fulfill the purpose of the request and will retain such information no longer than appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the request.

**TRANSFERS TO AGENTS:** Netronix Corporation, DBA eShow will obtain assurances from its agents that they will safeguard personal information consistently with this Policy. Examples of appropriate assurances that may be provided by agents include: a contract obligating the agent to provide at least the same level of protection as is required by the relevant Privacy Shield Framework Principles, being subject to EU Directive 95/46/EC (the EU Data Protection Directive), Privacy Shield certification by the agent, or being subject to another European Commission adequacy finding (e.g., companies located in Canada). Where Netronix Corporation, DBA eShow has knowledge that an agent is using or disclosing personal information in a manner contrary to this Policy, Netronix Corporation, DBA eShow will take reasonable steps to prevent or stop the use or disclosure.

**ACCESS AND CORRECTION:** Upon request, Netronix Corporation, DBA eShow will grant individuals reasonable access to personal information that it holds about them. In addition, Netronix Corporation, DBA eShow will take reasonable steps to permit individuals to correct, amend, or delete information that is demonstrated to be inaccurate or incomplete. These requests can be made by completing our International Consumer Service form at https://www.goeshow.com/contact_us.cfm or by calling the Netronix Corporation, DBA eShow office in the country where they reside and asking for consumer services.

**INFORMATION SECURITY:** Netronix Corporation, DBA eShow will take reasonable precautions to protect personal information in its possession from loss, misuse and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration and destruction.

**ENFORCEMENT:** Netronix Corporation, DBA eShow will conduct compliance audits of its relevant privacy practices to verify adherence to this Policy. Any employee that Netronix Corporation, DBA eShow determines intentionally violates this policy will be subject to disciplinary action up to and including termination of employment.

**CHILDREN:** The Sites are intended for business use, and we do not knowingly collect any Personal Information from children younger than the age of thirteen (13), or from children, who do not have the necessary ability to foresee the consequence of their data being processed, as required by applicable law.

**LIMITATIONS ON APPLICATION OF PRINCIPLES:** Adherence by Netronix Corporation, DBA eShow to these Privacy Shield Framework Principles may be limited (a) to the extent required or permitted by law or legal process, such as to respond to or investigate a legal or ethical obligation or request or pursuant to court orders, subpoenas, interrogatories or similar directive carrying the force of law; and (b) to the extent expressly permitted by an applicable law, rule or regulation.

**INTERNET PRIVACY:** Netronix Corporation, DBA eShow sees the Internet and the use of other technologies as valuable tools for communicating and interacting with consumers. Netronix Corporation, DBA eShow recognizes the importance of maintaining the privacy of information collected online and will adhere to the Privacy Shield Framework Principles as it pertains to governing the treatment of personal information collected through web sites that it operates. With respect to personal information that is transferred from the European Economic Area or Switzerland to the U.S. Netronix Corporation, DBA eShow’s Internet Privacy Policy is represented by the Privacy Shield Framework Principles and the Privacy Shield Policy that can be found herein.

**LEGAL PROTECTIONS AND REQUIRED DISCLOSURE** : Netronix Corporation, DBA eShow may access, use, preserve, transfer and disclose to third parties your Personal Information to: (1) satisfy any applicable law, regulation, subpoena, governmental request, or legal process if in our good faith opinion such is required or permitted by law; (2) protect and/or defend this Privacy Policy or other policies or terms of use applicable to our Sites, including investigations of potential violations thereof; (3) protect the safety, rights, property or security of Netronix Corporation, DBA eShow or any third party; and/or (4) detect, prevent or otherwise address fraud, security issues or breaches, or technical issues. This may include allowing third parties, such as copyright owners, Internet service providers, wireless service providers and/or law enforcement agencies, to access and use your Usage Information in order to identify you. We may take any of these steps without notice to you to the extent permitted by law.

## CONTACT INFORMATION

Questions or comments regarding this Policy should be submitted to the Netronix Corporation, DBA eShow Corporate Office.

By email to:  

By mail to:  
Netronix Corporation, DBA eShow  
Attn: Privacy Policy Officer  
5 Executive Court, Suite 2  
South Barrington, IL 60010

## EFFECTIVE DATE OF THIS POLICY

**April 20th, 2017**

## CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY

This Policy may be amended from time to time, consistent with the requirements of the Privacy Shield Framework Principles. We reserve the right to update this Privacy Policy at any time, without prior notice to you, to the extent permitted by applicable law and the principles of the Framework. We will notify the changes that we make to this Privacy Policy by posting the revised Privacy Policy on the Site, and such changes will be effective immediately unless otherwise stated.

_Last Revised: 4/1/2019_
